<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<LanguageData>

	<!-- Coherence -->
    <ABF_CoherenceGizmoLabel>Coherence</ABF_CoherenceGizmoLabel>
    <ABF_CoherenceDesc>Coherence is a measure of a pawn's intellectual integrity, the closest thing to sanity a synstruct has. Coherence degrades naturally over time and must be restored at an individual level. Poor coherence degrades efficiency, and may lead to health problems if allowed to persist for too long. High levels of coherence provides small benefits and mood bonuses, but also increases coherence loss - many pawns will be better off maintaining a middle of the road approach that maintains a stable existence.\n\nNote: Rules around coherence gain and loss can be found in the description for coherence retention efficiency in the info tab.</ABF_CoherenceDesc>
    <ABF_CoherenceTargetLabel>Target coherence</ABF_CoherenceTargetLabel>
    <ABF_CoherenceTargetLabelDesc>Click to set desired coherence level.</ABF_CoherenceTargetLabelDesc>

    <ABF_CoherenceEffectGizmoLabel>Average Coherence, {0}: {1} day(s)</ABF_CoherenceEffectGizmoLabel>
    <ABF_CoherenceEffectGizmoLabelPositive>Positive</ABF_CoherenceEffectGizmoLabelPositive>
    <ABF_CoherenceEffectGizmoLabelNegative>Negative</ABF_CoherenceEffectGizmoLabelNegative>
    <ABF_CoherenceEffectDesc>Average coherence is a measure of how well maintained this unit's core memory and internal systems have been over time, and changes based on the coherence level of the pawn. High levels will improve mood, while low levels will eventually degrade both mood and health. It rises if coherence is above 70% and falls if below 30%, and otherwise slowly returns to a baseline.\n\nNote: Coherence is a deeply personal quality for each individual and cannot be handled by others.</ABF_CoherenceEffectDesc>

    <!-- Reservoir -->
    <ABF_ReservoirGizmoLabel>Energy</ABF_ReservoirGizmoLabel>
    <ABF_ReservoirLevel>Reserve available: {0} Wd</ABF_ReservoirLevel>

    <!-- Minuteman Directive, 1.6+ -->
    <ABF_CommandToggleActivationDesc>Toggle whether this unit is active or not</ABF_CommandToggleActivationDesc>
    <ABF_CommandActiveLabel>Active</ABF_CommandActiveLabel>

</LanguageData>